A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Catalogued Reports, Reports 17727-19980 FA739G
Rockefeller Archive Center
- The Situation of the Theatre in Great Britain (Reports 019960), 1968
- Situation of the Theater and Music in Switzerland (Reports 019961), 1969
- The Situation of the Theater in Spain, (Reports 019962), 1969
- The Official School of Cinematography in Spain, (Reports 019963), 1969
- The Situation of Music in Spain (Reports 019964), 1969
- The Performing Arts Survey System, May 24 (Reports 019965), 1972
- The Comprehensive School Improvement Program (Reports 019966), 1971
- Leadership Development Program -- Staff Paper, Nov 10 (Reports 019967), 1971
- National Council of the Arts -- Program Paper and Board of Trustees Draft Resolution, n.d. (Reports 019968), undated
- Thoughts on Future Northeast Leadership Development Program, Nov 12 (Reports 019969), 1971
- Economic and Social Positions of the Artists and His Institutions. (Reports 019970), 1958
- Options for Opportunity Resources for the Arts, May 31 (Reports 019971), 1979
- Strengthening Communications for Public Enlightenment, May 26 (Reports 019972), 1959
- International Scientific, Educational and Cultural Exchange, May 27 (Reports 019973), 1959
- Humanistic Scholarship -- Conference of Humanities. (Reports 019974), 1958
- A Proposal for a Program in the Arts of National Scope, Jan 4 (Reports 019975), 1960
- The Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting -- September 28-29, 1956, Nov 21 (Reports 019976)
- The Cost of Supplies and Equipment as a Manageable Expense for Biomedical Research, May 13 (Reports 019977), 1975
- Minorities and Mathematics, Apr (Reports 019978), 1981
- Ford Foundation Conference on Minorities and Mathematics (Reports 019979), 1980
- Japanese-American Teacher Exchange Program (Reports 019980), 1967